Looks like you've been in a war.
I have. I lost someone.
Isn't this exactly what they'd do?
A near miss to make you
believe they were trying to kill you.
Or they were trying to
take me out to stop my op
and get their asset into downing street.
It's plausible. Come here.
It is my great pleasure
to announce my campaign
to be the next leader of our party.
Welcome to the Ryan
resistance movement.
Ryan says that he's managed
to get his hands on some...
Compromising footage of you.
Apparently. it was filmed in a hotel room.
Here he is. Monsieur Laurent sauverre.
He's a Swiss national.
Doesn't show up on our
radar or anywhere else.
That tells us something.
Come up to the ceremony. like I asked.
I can't. I'm in the middle of a campaign.
If you want me to bail you out
of a hole. you need to work for it.
In two days' time. we might have
a Russian asset in downing street.
The foreign secretary is
insisting you stand down.
You've been suspended.
Theoretically. it could be Imogen.
not Ryan. in Moscow's pocket.
With zak helping her.
The man who learned of our op
the day echo's cover was blown.
We're on our own.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Morning. 'Morning.'
any luck?
Well. I found zak's car rental receipts.
Yeah? 'He paid for the
Dubrovnik hire on his office amex.'
and then spent nothing
more on it for three days.
Unofficial business?
'Well. we can assume he
wasn't in portonovi for a spa day.'
anything your end?
Yeah. Looks like the
Swiss lawyer. sauverre.
owns an offshore called
global systems holdings.
Like a middle man for Ryan? 'Could be.'
if we really wanna find out. I
need to go fishing in Geneva.
All right. Call me when you land.
Hey. Good luck at northolt. yeah?
Excuse me. Just...
Can I help you. ma'am?
I'm here to see Rose trewen.
Go through. Thank you.
Unfinished business. Have
you not read your contract?
Kate. you've been suspended
from all official activity.
including contact with staff.
This isn't official. It's personal.
Can I see?
You've got two minutes. Ok.
Guess I must be contagious. Not to me.
Thanks for bringing her back.
I'm sorry you and rav took the rap.
Yeah. well. even zak knows he
can't shut down an entire desk.
Assuming you're going
to do what you're told.
Time to go. Why don't
you jump in the car?
I'll give you a lift back
into town. Not a good idea.
I'm not gonna kidnap her.
Julie. if anyone asks.
you travelled back with me.
Thanks. Rose.
If zak finds out you
were here. he will fire you.
We know for a fact that zak
was in portonovi two years ago
at the same time as Imogen
Conrad and kyril markov.
He was head of the Russia house.
he could have been there
for a hundred different reasons.
So why didn't he tell us he was there?
We know that echo's
cover was blown in Malta.
What if zak is passing
on operational intelligence
to kyril and Igor to help their
asset in the cabinet here?
That's a very big leap
of the imagination. Kate.
Will you give me access
to the office systems?
I just need to check to see
whether he filed any reports on this.
For Christ's sake.
We are not even supposed
to be having this conversation.
I've gotta go.
'This is Kate Henderson.
please leave a message.'
She throw the book at you for coming?
She's just trying to protect me. And you.
You're not giving up. are you?
I am too far into the
shit to Wade out now.
And I owe it to Lena. So do I.
I've taken some compassionate
leave. Isn't it up to me what I do with it?
I have to work out a way to
crack Igor's unit from the inside.
What can I do?
Locate mikhail.
He's afraid of his father.
and we know he's hiding
his relationship with his pa.
That makes him vulnerable.
And looking for a way out?
It's worth a shot.
To be honest. we're...
We're running out of options.
I'm impressed you still find the time.
Bit of a funny place to serve
me with a vote of no confidence.
I didn't want to go to your house.
We don't need to set
any more hares running.
And. er... Perhaps I was
too quick with the petition.
Look. I know we've had our differences.
But I also know you're
a decent man at heart.
You sound so convincing
when you say that
we both wanna win this.
But. Ryan. it has to be a fair fight.
It's a bit late for that. isn't it?
I was forced to use my dead son as
a defence against Russian collusion.
Only because you met
with krimsov off the record.
Yeah. another man who's lost a child.
A human being. whatever his politics.
Yeah. exactly.
Just because we're public servants.
it doesn't mean we're not
entitled to some privacy. Agreed?
Yeah. I still don't know
what you're getting at.
I think you do. Ryan.
Look. one of us is
gonna be prime minister.
So I suggest a truce
for the sake of the party.
Go on.
I'll drop the petition
if you agree to respect my personal life.
Look. your private life
really is none of my business.
Thank you.
But I think you over-estimate my powers.
I can't control what comes
to light in the public domain
any more than you can.
I'll take it that's a no?
I'm just not gonna make
you empty promises. Imogen.
I'm sure you'll handle whatever
blows you might have to take.
Just like I did.
'Where are you?'
I'm sorry. I had some
loose ends to tie up.
'You're not supposed
to be working. are you?'
I can't just abandon my
team. stu. 'Nor can I. Katie.
'I'm supposed to be helping
imo save the bloody country here.'
I'm doing pancakes. darling. ok?
I don't eat gluten. I just want toast. Right.
Look. I just need another
hour. and then I'll be back.
'I'll make it up to you.'
Well. you'd better. In kind!
See you. babe.
What's happened?
It's a temporary suspension.
Is it because your op
in Malta was blown?
My colleagues in Moscow say
it was by someone inside MI6.
You knew?
Who? I have no idea.
I only heard that Igor's running
a sealed unit on the eighth floor.
They put out the Malta alert
when they were tipped off
about your agent in the villa.
Is there any chance they
know you're working for me?
Not yet. But it's only a matter of time.
Is there any way we can
hack into Igor's unit? No.
None of his generation
trust digital records.
What about the paper versions?
The unit is completely off limits.
Staff. reporting lines. I've never
even been to the eighth floor.
There's always a way
in. Finance? Travel?
Yes. But also on the eighth floor.
If we can place Igor
and any cabinet ministers
or sis staff in the same
place at the same time.
then we might have something.
Maybe. But I have to go back to Moscow.
#extremely fucking stupid.
Russia's infected half of
Europe and all of america
with bullshit like this.
How'd it go?
It didn't.
No guarantees. just an
outright denial of any knowledge.
Cool as a fucking cucumber.
We've got a new problem.
Have you seen this?
Three small boat migrants broke
out of the scamp ton barracks.
dragged two teenage girls
behind a bus stop and raped them.
The only thing is.
lincolnshire police don't
have a record of the crime.
So it's fake? I've asked the
security services to look into it.
But it looks that way. yeah.
Of course. it hasn't stopped
Ryan from trying to pin it on you.
"If I become prime minister.
I'll call for an immediate rethink"
"of our soft-touch immigration policy."
Yeah. It's a nice divert away
from the krimsov scandal.
He just warned me it
would come to blows.
All right.
Let's deal him one back.
'Hey. I've found mikhail.
'I checked the flight
logs. He's in Helsinki.'
can you go there and get eyes on him?
Today?
'Yep. As soon as I've finished here.'
before you log off. I need
you to pull up an agent report
that was filed last year.
It's about the svr hq in Moscow.
'What am I looking for?'
The new wing construction.
There were building plans in the file.
'Got it.' Thanks. Julie.
'Gchq have traced it back
to a website in Karachi.
'Then lev amatov's outposts
picked it up and went to work.'
ok.
I mean. are you sure that you
want to go in hard over this?
'Absolutely.
'We question its authenticity and
show how rash and stupid he is.
'Then we finish him off with
a statement of no confidence.'
but what if it doesn't finish him off
and it just pushes him into
releasing the other video?
'I'm not convinced he will. Stuart.
'And anyway. I'm
prepared to take that risk.
'I don't see what other options we have.'
ok. hang on.
I'm going out. No.
you're not going out. no.
We're having a family
brunch... Lunch soon.
But mum's not even here.
I'm supposed to see Jay.
You can see Jay tomorrow.
So I'm under fucking house arrest?
Excuse me. you will
be under house arrest
if you carry on using
language like that. thank you.
'Is everything all right?'
Yeah. sorry... where were we?
Are you sure you wanna do this?
'Yes. Call a press
conference for five o'clock.
'and let's take him down.'
all right. Ok. fine.
Is this video AI. foreign secretary?
Are the refugee rapists actually real?
There's a backlash starting.
You were concerned. like any
responsible person would be.
Narrative favours the brave.
so you've just got to own it.
Yeah. well. now it's playing
very nicely into Imogen's hands.
Look at that.
"Border safety depends
on facts. not fiction."
Don't worry about Imogen.
Just stick to the plan.
I thought lev was
supposed to be helping us.
Nearly half a million
people liked your post.
So the issue's real.
even if the footage isn't.
Lev's on your side. Mine or yours?
I just don't need any more
heat about Russian contacts
after the krimsov disaster.
For god's sake.
Why's everyone always trying to
paint lev as some kremlin puppet?
Because this country likes heroes
and villains. it always has done.
Well. on that note...
are you ready for daddy?
Yeah. Thanks for coming.
Remember. rule number
one. it's all about him.
Rule number two. it's
all about him. Yeah.
Thank you.
There you are. Finally. Sorry.
How are the kids? Fiona
won't answer my texts.
Well. no. cos she's upstairs sulking
because I said she
couldn't go and see Jay.
So that you can hear
right now is protest music.
Where are you going?
Yeah. so. I had a last-minute phone call
about an emergency summit.
so I might be gone for
quite some time. I'm sorry.
That's ok. go. Ok.
I think he's maybe
feeling a little bit invisible.
so have a chat with him.
Yeah. Love you.
Got it.
Julie.
'I've emailed you the svr plans.
but they don't tell us much.'
great. You're a star. I'll
take a look at them in a bit.
'Yeah. I've got to go.
I'll call from Helsinki.'
yeah. Bye.
You all right. love?
Shall we get a pizza and
watch something together?
What. so you can just sit
on your laptop and work?
You won't be able to concentrate anyway.
Fiona.
Fi. the whole street can hear.
Fi?
'Hiya. this is fi. please leave a message.'
'I'm driving.' Fiona's not here.
'Where is she?'
I don't know. She's not
answering her phone.
'Right. well. she's
probably headed to Jay's.'
do you have his details? 'No. I haven't.'
well. I'll give her half an hour.
and if she's not back by then.
I'll have to call round some of her friends
and see if they've got his number.
'Look. she'll be all right.
'She's headstrong. but she's not stupid.
'Bit like her mum.'
I'd just like to thank you
all for joining us today
and braving the brisk Yorkshire weather.
But we're here to talk about my father.
My father is the embodiment
of our party's commitment
to equality and aspiration.
And his father. my grandad.
was a coal miner in a
region not too far from here.
And dad. he started
out as a union steward.
He then went on to build
a series of companies
that pay fair wages to
thousands of British people.
He knows that community is everything.
And his ambitious renovation on
this estate will create affordable homes
alongside vital public services.
This is just the latest example
of his generosity of spirit.
Now. since I've raised
the prospect of increasing
the tax rate for the richest
people in our society.
the right-wing press have gone to town.
I'm a communist. A corbynite.
Well. I hope I'm slightly
better dressed than that.
But like my dad.
who is the biggest donor to
the party for working people.
I just want to see
the most privileged
helping the least privileged.
That's the country I want to live in.
and that's the government I want to lead.
Anyway. time to get my
hands dirty. Thank you.
You've got my vote. Ryan!
Thank you. I'll hold you to that.
Well done. Ryan.
Foreign secretary. do you
know that riots have broken out
in lincolnshire and hartlepool?
Do you bear some responsibility for that?
Well. right now. romilly.
we're here to celebrate my
father and these renovations.
But do you regret jumping
on the bandwagon?
I mean. there's a danger
the situation's spiralling
out of control now.
Another time.
You bloody idiot. What
happened to due diligence?
Have you had chance to
think about this loan yet?
Because I'm running out of time.
Your comrades won't bail you out?
You asked me to come today.
and I came. What more do you want?
I asked you to come
because I want you to
believe in what I'm doing.
Not just kiss my arse.
Well. if you're not gonna help.
we can just kiss goodbye
to number 10! "We"?
Look. you've sponged off
your wife for long enough.
It's about time you learned to
stand on your own two feet. son!
You'll thank me for it one day.
Bye. Bye.
Where are you?
I just left Jay's. I'm walking home.
I'm really sorry your dad
and I had to work today.
but please don't sneak
off without telling us.
I'm not a kid. mum.
'I know you're not.' Then
stop treating me like one.
No-one else I know
has a weekend curfew.
'It's... it's not a curfew.'
I just want to spend time with
you. Is that such a bad thing?
Fi?
'Fi?'
I think there's a guy following me.
What guy? 'I don't know.'
I think I saw him on
our street when I left.
Where are you? Well street.
Go to the corner shop. tell the
owner that you don't feel safe. ok?
Just stay there. I'm coming right now.
Ok.
Is he still following you? 'Yeah.'
don't panic. He's probably
just trying to spook you.
'How do you know that?'
Just trust me. you'll be fine.
We've gotta go. Come on. Where?
Questions later. Now. Gus!
Come on.
Hello? 'Are you inside?'
yeah. There's nobody
here. 'Ok. I'm on my way.'
hello?
Hello?
Are you still there. fi?
'Yeah.' ok.
He's come inside.
Right. I'm almost there.
You ok? Yeah.
Wait in the car.
Fuck this.
Don't even think about it.
Tell your bosses. if I ever see
anyone near my family again.
I will break their fucking
necks. Understood?
That man was Russian. A sort of officer.
A police officer?
No. He's an intelligence agent.
He works for the Russian secret service.
Why was he following me?
So. I told you that I'm
a civil servant. right?
And that's true.
But there's a bit more
that you don't know about.
So. I work for the British
secret intelligence service.
I. er... I recruit people
who work for different organisations.
mainly Russian ones.
so we can gather information to stop...
What? What's so funny?
You're a spy? Mum.
You're... you're classic.
You think I'm lying to you?
Come on. Spies don't... Don't what?
Don't keep their passports
in a safe or travel abroad
at a moment's notice or speak Russian?
But you're right. I'm
not a spy. I handle spies.
They do most of the risky stuff.
but sometimes. as their
handler. I get put in the spotlight.
Why are they watching us?
Er. it's a message to
me. from his handlers.
to let me know that
they're keeping tabs on me.
He would have never have hurt you. ok?
But I am gonna report it
to the police just in case.
and my office.
Even though I'm not
gonna be in for a while.
Why not?
It's complicated.
Look. I just want you to
know that we are safe. ok?
Ok? Yeah.
Is there anything that
you want to ask me?
Does dad know what you
do? Of course he does.
But... I have to keep the
day-to-day details to myself.
Have you ever shot anybody?
I've been trained to. just in case.
It's a lot harder than it looks.
I know it's a lot to take in.
Come here.
Monsieur sauverre. Harris
Khan. It's really good to meet you.
Laurent. please.
Enchante. Come in. please.
Your first time in Geneva?
No. I've... Done some
business here before.
But your private banks.
they're getting very cautious these days
about the purity of their cash flow.
Sensitive investments are my speciality.
I take that to mean you
think you can help me?
Absolutely. We have all
necessary protocols in place.
I took the Liberty of
doing a little ground work.
A potential strategy for your investment.
Very good.
Tonight. my colleagues
and I take the difficult decision
to demand that a senior
minister resigns from his post
and withdraws from
the leadership contest.
As the home secretary.
this country's security is my top priority.
The foreign secretary's decision
to meet the Russian
foreign minister in secret
is part of a wider pattern
of questionable judgements.
Just today. he put his support
behind an almost certainly fake video
that is now causing
unrest across the country.
Now. at a time when the world
has never felt more dangerous.
we believe that this disqualifies him
from holding high office of any kind.
She deserves everything
she's gonna get.
Agreed.
'Hey. this is rav. please leave
a message or send a text.'
You remember Jim?
He's staying outside
tonight and tomorrow.
Raqqa. Kate.
How could I forget? Come in.
Try not to worry. Jim's
the very best we've got.
Do you want a cup
of tea? No. no. I'm fine.
How's Fiona doing?
She's worn out. but
she's... She's all right.
I just can't believe
they came after us here.
I know.
I've briefed zak and the chief.
The foreign office should know. too.
We're in uncharted waters here.
And there's something else.
So. I looked through
zak's reports from 2024.
He logged the trip to Dubrovnik.
A routine meet with the
head of Croatian intelligence.
But there is no mention of
any business in portonovi.
Well. he was there off-grid for three days
before he flew back out of Dubrovnik.
which is a very long
time to go awol in this job.
Yes. it is.
Is he still at the office? He
was logged in when I left.
So let's start a fire and
try to smoke him out.
Hiya.
I'll head back and see if he's still there.
Hi. Hello. Rose.
Stuart.
Who's the... Who's the guy on the door?
Special ops security.
Ok. Where's fi? Is she...?
She's asleep. she's fine. I'm
gonna go and speak to her.
No. no. no. leave her. Leave
her for now. She's all right.
I need a fucking drink.
So sorry. Rose. I'll leave you to it.
So. how was it?
Er. yeah. you know.
the pm's kicked off. but
Walker gave us no choice.
So it is up to the party now.
There you are. No. I'm all right.
Looks like you could do with it. Ok? Ok.
I just wish that I'd been here
when you told the
kids that you were 007.
They don't think I'm that cool.
I can't believe this has happened.
No. me neither.
I hate that I've exposed us all like this.
Why don't you stop?
Well. and do what?
Just do something else.
Just do something less dangerous.
Love.
Here we go.
'As the home secretary.
'this country's security is my top priority.
'The foreign secretary's decision
'to meet with the
Russian foreign minister
'in secret is part of a wider
pattern of questionable judgements.
'Just today. he put his support
'behind an almost certainly fake video
'that is now causing
unrest across the country.'
fuck.
Everything ok?
Yeah. yeah. yeah. I just
need to make a work call.
Ok.
'..In some cases. disorder
and in some cases. riots
'that are now beginning to spread.'
Hey.
Where are you?
Just got home.
I've been trying to call
you. 'I know. I'm sorry.'
don't worry. because I've got good news.
I managed to hack sauverre's laptop.
What did you find?
Mate. It's a fucking jackpot.
Ryan Walker took
payments from Igor borodin.
'Now. sauverre brokered the
entire deal through his offshore.'
fuck. 'Yeah.'
have you spoken to Julie?
No. not yet. Do you want me to tell her?
No. no. no. Don't...
Don't speak to anyone.
Ok. Kate. are you all right?
I don't know yet. I've
got one more thing to do.
but then maybe we can
meet at yours in an hour?
'Yeah. Sounds good.'
I'll send you the screen grabs
in the meanwhile. yeah? Ok.
Ok. See you soon. bye.
Game over. Ryan.
Every room on the eighth
floor has its own bathroom.
Typical Russian bosses.
Except this one.
If it isn't a private office.
it must be for records.
Look for Igor's travel file.
If we can match his travel with
someone in the UK government...
I won't have long. I'll need dates.
When was his special unit set up?
Straight after he recruited
the agent. I assume.
I'm working on it.
We need to talk about the risks.
I think we both know the risks.
Yeah.
I'll be in contact.
Rav?
'Hey. this is rav. please
leave a message.'
Subtitles by accessibility@itv.Com
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm